How can you cancel your Bajaj Finance insurance policy? Today in this video
I explained step by step friends, it is
very easy, whenever you take any type of
loan from Bajaj Finance or get
any EMI done, then you are
added to an insurance policy there,
if you want to cancel it, then what will you have to do.
In today's video I will
tell you, if
you want to cancel your insurance policy in Bajaj Finance,
then you have to take care of some buttons,
whenever you
get your insurance, on the date when your
insurance policy is issued, friends,
you have to do this within 15 to 30 days from that date, only then your
money will be refunded and your
policy will be able to be cancelled, this is
called free lock, friends, and
it is generally for 15 to 30 days,
in between this you have to follow this process
and cancel your insurance policy,
if it is more
than a month, friends, then
this policy will not be cancelled and you will have to get
your  You will not get any refund for this,
first of all you all have to open the Bajaj Finance app, you will get
some
type of entry like this, after logging in
you will go to this page, an
option is given in Me Relation, how much is
your EMI, how much is
your loan, which insurance policy you have,
everything will be visible, so here in Me Relation
itself you will get to see
which policy you want to cancel,
sir will take the details, you can see,
I have an insurance policy running of Rs.
2787, friends, I want to cancel this,
okay, I want to cancel this, friends, you
can see below, here you people are
given the option of view, you people have to
click on view and a page to check your
insurance policy in detail will
open in front of you,
here you will be told
which insurance is running for you, simply you have to
click on the right arrow given here, after that you will be asked to wait for a few seconds
here,
after that the complete details of your insurance policy will be displayed to
you, friends  It will be displayed in front of you
that how much is the insurance policy, how much will
you have to pay for it, what will be
its starting date and
what will be the rate, what is the date, you will get
to see all this here, you will come down friends, you
can see here that the option of Surendra is also given
or cancel policy, sometimes the
option will not be shown here, friends, so
I will directly tell you what to do, right now, cancel is
written here, so
click on cancel, you will see here
that the CPC one is here,
so come down here friends, here
Surendra cancel policy is written,
you have to click on it,
after clicking on it, friends, you
can see here that you people are being told
that you have to make a request, so
if you do not see such an option, then you
can request directly, right,
I will go to my account, there you will go to hill pen
support, then you will be
able to request there also, right now friends,
you have to make a request here, if
you get this process then you have to
follow this, here friends, you can see, the
option of insurance will appear and the
insurance which is going on with you will be  You have to
click on this and come below it.
After coming down, friends,
click on the proceed button here, that is, we
request
you people here and everyone will have to select in edit up.
In the complete type, you people have to
select insurance cancellation
and give everyone a reason. Basically,
why do you want to cancel it, then you
people can select it as per your wish.
After selecting, you will get
to see the option below.
After this, friends, whatever
is your insurance cancellation description, you can
write it a little, which
can be shortened by other voices. Okay, after that, you have to
come down. After coming down, friends, here
you do not have to do anything in the document password
and come down. After coming down,
friends, you people will have to provide alternate contact
details. Okay,
give the alternate email ID and after coming down,
give the alternate mobile number
and click on submit below here.
Click on submit. Friends,
you will get to see here
that your request is  It has been successfully
released and you will be provided with a
service request number here
and your concern will be
resolved and your policy will be
cancelled. In this way, you
can follow the process to cancel the policy.